in this video I'll show you how to
在这段视频中 我将向您展示如何
import a sequence of images into shot
将一系列图像导入快照
cut and have it be converted into just a
剪切并将其转换为仅一个
video so to do this we have a sequence
视频要做到这一点 我们有一个序列
of images here if I just push forward
如果我往前推的话
this is just looking at them in the
这只是看着他们在
picture viewer and what we need to do is
图片浏览器 我们需要做的是
just drag and drop the very first image
只需拖放第一张图像
of the sequence into our playlist area
进入我们的播放列表区域
so you need to click on playlist and
所以你需要点击播放列表和
then drag that in and then while that
然后把它拖进去 然后当它
selected click on properties if you
如果选择了以下选项 请单击属性
don't have a properties tab you can also
没有属性选项卡 您还可以
get to it by clicking properties up here
单击此处的属性即可访问它
and then we just check this checkbox
然后我们只需选中此复选框
next to image sequence and this has how
旁边的图像序列和这是如何进行的
many pictures do you want per frame this
这一帧你想要多少张照片？
is only a 20 frame movie but I'll just
只是一部20帧的电影 但我会
say 1 you could if you wanted to go
如果你想去 就说1你可以去
slower you could have more play but then
慢一点 你可以有更多的玩耍 但是
we just click and it'll play through
我们只需点击一下 它就会播放完
very quickly or we can hold and click
非常快 或者我们可以按住并点击
and look through with those and then
带着这些看过去 然后
once that's done if we go back to our
一旦我们完成了 如果我们回到我们的
playlist that's now converted we can
现在已转换的播放列表 我们可以
left-click and drag it down to the
左键单击并将其向下拖动到
timeline and now our videos here in the
时间线 现在我们在这里的视频
timeline and we can zoom in since it's
时间线 我们可以放大 因为它是
very very small and we can see that
非常非常小 我们可以看到
whole video here if we want to just
完整的视频 如果我们想要
export this short video now we could
现在导出此短视频 我们可以
leave it just like this if we're not
如果我们不是 就让它像这样
doing any more edits we can just click
进行更多编辑时 我们只需点击
up on export and then we can click on
在导出时打开 然后我们可以点击
YouTube which want to export for YouTube
想要为YouTube导出的YouTube
for example click export file and then
例如 单击导出文件 然后
give it a name just call this test under
给它起个名字 把这个测试叫做
videos and hit save we'll just call this
视频和点击保存我们就称其为
test and then click Save and that will
测试 然后单击保存 这将
export shouldn't take long at all with a
出口应该不会花很长时间
tiny video like this and now that video
像这样的小视频和现在的那个视频
is done and if we go into the videos on
已经完成 如果我们深入到视频中
my computer where I saved that we now
我把它保存在我的电脑里 现在
have a folder called test oh I put it in
我有一个名为TEST的文件夹哦 我把它放进去了
a folder called test and also I already
一个名为TEST的文件夹 还有我已经
have a folder called test but now we
有一个名为test的文件夹 但现在我们
have this video and there it is a video
有这段视频 那就是一段视频
from an image sequence if you have any
从图像序列（如果有）
questions or comments please leave them
问题或评论请留下
below appreciate you watching we'll
下面感谢您的收看 我们将
catch you in the next video
在下一个视频中与您联系
you
你